{
    "subject": "Elissa_Ambrose",
    "predicate": "isCitizenOf",
    "object": "Canada",
    "human_readable": "Elissa Ambrose is a citizen of Canada.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9872114062309265,
            "question": "Does Elissa Ambrose have Canadian citizenship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9693787097930908,
            "question": "Is Elissa Ambrose Canadian?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8796161413192749,
            "question": "Does Elissa Ambrose live in Canada?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8730878233909607,
            "question": "What country is Elissa Ambrose a citizen of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7704717516899109,
            "question": "Is Canada Elissa Ambrose's home country?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5749561786651611,
            "question": "Where was Elissa Ambrose born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5564717650413513,
            "question": "Where does Elissa Ambrose reside?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5140933990478516,
            "question": "What is Elissa Ambrose's nationality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5083349943161011,
            "question": "What is Elissa Ambrose's nationality status?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49843505024909973,
            "question": "To which nation does Elissa Ambrose belong?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Elissa Ambrose is a citizen of Canada.",
            "html": "yago_25845_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Elissa Ambrose's nationality status?",
            "html": "yago_25845_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Elissa Ambrose's nationality?",
            "html": "yago_25845_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where does Elissa Ambrose reside?",
            "html": "yago_25845_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25845_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25845_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25845_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25845_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25845_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25845_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25845_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25845_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25845_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25845_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format with my evaluation:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nMy reasoning is as follows:\n\n* The documents contain multiple mentions of Elissa Ambrose's birthplace, which is consistently stated to be Montreal, Canada. \n* There are no statements in the documents that contradict this information or suggest that she has another nationality.\n* Therefore, the statement that Elissa Ambrose is a citizen of Canada is supported by the information provided in the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information provided across the documents indicates that Elissa Ambrose was born in Montreal, Canada. This strongly supports the statement that she is a Canadian citizen."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}